The Amanda Steele Show.
Today's
goes to Ernie Hudson's
jeans.
No, I'm not talking about his Levi's
denim on denim on denim.
I'm actually talking about his G-E-N-E-S.
This man is 78 years old.
Have you seen him in his black fitted tees?
I mean, he would give 50 a run for the money
in the G-Unit bar strap chain tops
if he put it on. I really feel like.
This is beyond Black Don't Crack.
This man doesn't look a day over 56.
And the fact that he is a two-time cancer survivor,
which means he probably had to really
significantly change his diet.
He's got to be on a Dr. Sebi.
That ain't just push-ups and water.
But Don't.
Goes to Tyrese's phone carrier
for providing him with data.
Tyrese was not pleased
at the fact that Joe Biden
recognized March 31st
as a day for trans visibility.
March 31st has been trans visibility day.
It's Easter that moves.
If y'all want to ban trans visibility day
because it was already scheduled
to be on March 31st,
which ended up landing
on the same day as Easter,
then let's go ahead and ban
these other actual holidays
that also fall on March 31st.
You know what we got to get out of here?
Oranges and lemons day.
Why are we celebrating fruit
on the Lord's resurrection day?
I don't recall reading about mimosas
being served at the last supper.
I think we need to put a stop
to National Crayon Day.
Easter is about coloring eggs,
not coloring books.
Just foolishness.
We are, we are, we are.